<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Nagngangawngaw</string>
    <string name="user_name">Username</string>
    <string name="gender">Gender</string>
    <string name="weight">Weight</string>
    <string name="create">Create</string>
    <string name="slim">Slim Body</string>
    <string name="lean">Lean Body</string>
    <string name="bulk">Bulk Body</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="shop">Shop</string>
    <string name="profile">Profile</string>

    chest / male
    <string name="bench_press">Step 1: Lay flat on a bench and have your feet flat on the floor. The bar, when racked, will be slightly behind your head. It is important to use a spotter for this exercise, especially if you are using a free bar or dumbbells, to eliminate the chance of dropping the weight on yourself. / Step 2: Once you have lifted the weight off of the rack, the bar will be directly over the center of your chest. Keep your head on the bench at all times throughout the movement. Once you have the bar steady, slowly lower it to about chest level, if you are able to. your arms pointed outward as the bar drops. Upon reaching the bottom the movement, press the bar back up to an extended position, focusing on driving the bar upwards with your chest and arms.</string>
    <string name="incline_press">Step 1: Lift the barbell off of the rack and slowly lower it to about 3 inches above your clavicle (just below your Adam\'s apple) and then press the bar back to the start position. DO NOT TOUCH THE BAR TO YOUR UPPER CHEST (this causes unneeded stress on your shoulder joints and takes the tension away from your upper pec muscles, which are what want to doing the work!). sure that when you are lowering the bar that you do so in a slow and controlled fashion. Conversely, when you press the bar upward, you want to do so in an explosive fashion.</string>
    <string name="incline_db">Step 1: This exercise is very similar to the regular barbell bench press except that you will be using an incline free weight bench press machine and your upper chest will be the muscle group worked instead of your middle chest. / Step 2: Lift the dumbbell off of the rack and slowly lower it to about 3 inches above your clavicle (just below your Adam\'s apple) and then press bar back to the start position. DO NOT TOUCH YOUR UPPER CHEST (this causes unneeded shoulder joints and takes the tension away from your upper pec muscles, which are what want to doing the work!). that when you are lowering the dumbbell that you do in a slow and controlled fashion. Conversely, when you press the dumbbell upward, you want to do so in an explosive fashion.</string>
    <string name="cable_cf">Step 1: This exercise is performed using the cable pulley machine that has a pulley on two opposite sides. Set each pulley up so that it is locked in the high position (if you are not sure how to do this, ask a trainer at the gym you workout at to assist you). / Step 2: While standing, grab each high pulley using a small one- and attachment for each hand. The position our body will be in will look like a giant letter. Slowly bring your arms together in a slow and controlled fashion. / Step 3: While doing so, visualize that you are hugging a giant tree trunk. At the peak of this movement, really flex your pec muscles together for a one- count and then return to the start position and repeat.</string>
    <string name="dumbbell_fly">Step 1: To perform dumbbell flies pick, up a relatively light weight in each hand. You will need to experiment to determine how much weight is your flies. with a lighter weight then slowly work your way up. Lie down on a weight bench and raise both dumbbells straight up over your chest with your arms straight. / Step 2: This is your starting position. Spread both arms outward in a wide arc until your arms are out at your sides. Your arms can be slightly bent. This is the fly part of the dumbbell flies. It is called that because you look like you are flying Follow the same arc back up until the dumbbells return to the starting position. This is one repetition of the dumbbell fly.</string>
    <string name="push_ups">Step 1. Lie prone with your arms straight, your palms flat on the floor, and your hands shoulder-width apart (or wider). / Step 2. Hold your feet together or very slightly spread: Inhale and bend your elbows to bring your torso near the floor, avoiding extreme hyperextension of your spine Push yourself back to arms, extended position, exhaling as you complete the movement.</string>
    <string name="pec_df">Step 1: Sit on the machine\'s seat and press your elbows into the pads, relaxing your forearms and wrists. / Step 2: Inhale and force the pads together until they touch in front of your chest. Exhale as you complete the movement.</string>
    <string name="decline_pu">Step 1: Place your feet on a bench or any elevated step and get into a standard pushup position. / Step 2: Lower your body until your chest nearly touches the floor, pause, then push yourself back to the starting position Maintain proper form throughout by preventing your hips from Sag gin at any point, keep your core stiff by bracing your abdominal muscles and straighten your legs while placing your weight on your toes.</string>
    <string name="incline_pu">Step 1: Place your hands on a bench and get into a standard pushup position. / Step 2: Lower your body until your chest nearly touches the bench, pause, then push yourself back to the starting position. Maintaining roper form throughout by preventing your Hips from Sagging at any point, keep your core stiff by bracing your abdominal muscles and straighten your legs while your weight on your toes. Repeat.</string>
    <string name="dumbbell_po">Step 1: This is very similar to the bent arm barbell pullovers, except that you will be using a dumbbell instead of a barbell. Lie flat on your back on a flat bench. Begin by holding the dumbbell above your chest with your elbows slightly bent. Slowly lower the dumbbell back so as to stretch your arms and the dumbbell) back behind your head as far as you can reach. / Step 2: Your arms and the dumbbell will actually go behind/ above your head and will drop down below the bench this will really give you a great stretch! Return the dumbbell to the start position slowly, focusing on keeping your elbows locked in the slightly bent position.</string>
    
    Abs / male
    <string name="abs_insu">Step 1: Lie back on the decline bench. Position hands overhead. Knees are bent. / Step 2: Raise your upper body upward while keeping your lower back on the bench. Hold for one second. Return to starting position.</string>
    <string name="abs_c">Step 1: While lying on your back, straighten your legs, raise your heels an inch off the floor, and place your hands by your sides. / Step 2: Keeping your arms parallel to the floor, lift your torso and legs so they form a e. As you raise yourself, bend your knees and pull them up toward your chest.</string>
    <string name="abs_lr">Step 1: Lie down on the floor. Extend your legs straight. Position your hands behind your head. / Step 2: Raise your upper body upward. Hold for one second. Return to starting position.</string>
    <string name="abs_sj">Step 1: Sit on the side of the bench. Hold onto the side of the bench with both hands at shoulder width. Lie back and raise your legs until you reach a position balance. / Step 2: Bend your knees towards your upper body. At the same time, move upper body forward to maintain position of balance. Hold for none second. Return to starting position</string>
    <string name="abs_sb">Step 1: Lie on your side. Make sure one leg is on top of the other. Position the forearm on the floor perpendicular with your body. / Step 2: Use your forearm to lift your upper body of the ground. The other arm is placed on the side of your body. Your body should be straight. Only your forearm and the side of your foot should be touching the floor. Hold this position.</string>
    <string name="abs_ct">Step 1: Sit down with your feet flat and knees bent. Grasp a weighted with both hands. Lean back slightly as you fully extend your arms straight in front of you. / Step 2: Twist your torso in one direction. Hold for one second. / Step 3: Return to starting position. Twist your torso in the other direction. Hold for one second. Return to starting position.</string>
    <string name="abs_thr">Step 1: Lie on your back with your hands underneath your tailbone and have your legs straight upward, as illustrated / Step 2: Pull your navel inward and flex your glutes as you lift your hips just a few inches the floor. Then lower your hips.</string>
    <string name="abs_p">Step 1: Begin by lying flat on the ground, stomach down, with your knees fully extended. / Step 2: Bend your arms and position your elbows directly beneath your shoulders, supporting yourself with your forearms. / Step 3: Clench your fists and raise yourself up until your only points of contact with the ground are your toes, elbows, forearms, and fists. / Step 4: Maintaining a flat back, inhale and squeeze your abs and glutes as tightly as possible. / Step 5: Remain in this position for the duration of your set.</string>
    <string name="abs_ps">Step 1: Lie on your side, your legs fully extended. / Step 2: Position your elbow beneath your shoulder, and point your forearm in front of you with a clenched fist. Place your other hand on your hip. / Step 3: Raise yourself up so that your only points of contact with the ground are your feet, elbow, forearm, and fist. / Step 4: Raise your hip upwards to straighten out your body. / Step 5: Maintain this position for the duration of your set.</string>

    Back / male
    <string name="back_d">a</string>
    <string name="back_bor">Step 1: With your feet shoulder-width apart and your knees bent roughly,keep your torso straight with a slight arch in your back as you lean forward at the hips. Your torso should be, at this point, roughly parallel to the floor. / Step 2: Slowly retract your shoulder blades as to have the bar pull up to the lower part of your sternum. Try not to use your arm muscles, and focus on getting most activity out of your middle-back muscles. / Step 3: Pause at the top where your chest should be sticking out toward the bar. Then, slowly return to the starting position Whale keeping your torso in the same position throughout the movement.</string>
    <string name="back_bs">Step 1: Stand upright and hold two fairly Heavy barbell at your sides, with your palms facing each other (neutral-grip). / Step 2: Keep your shoulders relaxed Shrug your shoulders as if you were trying to touch them to your ears. / Step 3: Hold the top most position, then gradually lower them to the starting position. Do not bend your elbows or shift your head forward during the motion. Repeat.</string>
    <string name="back_sr">Step 1: Place your feet on the platform, keeping. a slight bend in your knees and making your posture "tall". Grasp the handles and extend your back forward while keeping your shoulders slightly retracted, and then pull your elbows in and back toward the sides of your torso the handles should come all the way in until it reaches your navel. / Step 2: Hold the position for a second before returning back out, keeping the movement under control: your arms returning to the extended position, your back going slightly forward; and with your knees slightly bent. / Step 3: Repeat for the desired number of reps.</string>
    <string name="back_oadr">Step 1: Use your non-dominant hand to hold dumbbell, while placing your dominant hand and knee on a bench, as illustrated. / Step 2: Keep your back flat as you let the dumbbell hang down to your side so your arm lines up just in front of your shoulder. Step 3: Pull the dumbbell upward and back toward your hip while keeping your elbow close to your body. Focus on using your upper-back muscles in doing this motion. Pause, then slowly return to the starting position</string>
    <string name="back_lpd">Step 1: Sitting on a bench, grab a bar with a false overhand thumb on the same side as your fingers shoulder-width grip. / Step 2: As you pull your shoulder blades together and down, while sticking your Chest Out, pull the bar to your chest. Then, pause with the bar an inch or so from your chest, and slowly let it rise to where it began. Throughout, keep your chest out.</string>
    <string name="back_tbor">Step 1: Straddle a T-Bar-Row machine and grab handles with an overhand grip. Make sure you are standing with your feet shoulder-width apart and your knees slightly bent as shown. / Step 2: Keep your back flat and bend your waist until your upper body is about 45 degrees from the vertical, the bar hanging at arm\'s length directly below your shoulders. / Step 3: Then, squeezing yout shoulder blades together, lift the bar as close as you can to your lower chest. Pause, them slowly lower the bar back to starting position</string>
    <string name="back_bsm">Step 1: Lie prone on the floor. Fully extend your arms in front of you. / Step 2: Raise your legs and upper body towards the ceiling. Hold for one second. Return to starting position</string>
    <string name="back_sbh">Step 1: Lie down on your chest on a swiss- Ball and place your hands at the side of your head. Keep your legs extended straight behind with a small bend at the knees if needed. / Step 2: Raise your chest up off the ball and rotate your upper body to one side at the same time. / Step 3: Return back to starting position, and rotate to the other side. Keep the ball stable and avoid having it move.</string>

    Shoulder / male
    <string name="shoulder_bp">Step 1: Start by sitting on the bench (with back support). Grasp the barbell using an overhand grip. Hold the dumbbells above the shoulders slightly in front of you, pointing the elbows towards the floor. / Step 2: Push the barbell up and overhead so that the arms are fully extended. After a pause lower the weights to the starting position.</string>
    <string name="shoulder_sfp">Step 1: Sitting on an upright bench. Grab the barbell with wider then shoulder width grip. Push the barbell directly upward until it is at arms length above your shoulders. / Step 2: Lower the barbell down to the front of your shoulders then press it back to starting position.</string>
    <string name="shoulder_sdp">Step 1: Position yourself on a bench or chair with your back upright and straight. Grasp a dumbbell in each hand and hold them just outside of each shoulder with your thumbs pointing in toward each other. / Step 2: Simply press the dumbbells up over your head and return to the start position just outside your shoulders.</string>
    <string name="shoulder_drdr">Step 1: Sit on a bench, inclined forward, foot on the floor together. Raise the dumbbells to the side is you can keeping your hands straight and slowly do back to your start position.</string>
    <string name="shoulder_lr">Step 1: Stand with your feet slightly spread. Keep your back straight, your arms hanging at our sides, holding one dumbbell in each and: Raise the dumbbell to shoulder level keeping your elbows slightly bent. / Step 2: Return to the starting position</string>
    <string name="shoulder_fr">Step 1: Stand with feet slightly apart. Hold the dumbbells with your palms down (overhand gips), resting the dumbbells on your thighs or slightly to your sider Inhale and alternate sides raising the dumbbells forward to shoulder height Exhale as you complete the movement.</string>
    <string name="shoulder_ar">Step 1: Sit on a flat bench and hold a pair of dumbbells at the level of your shoulders. Your palms should be facing the inward, and your elbows should point to the side. / Step 2: Turn both of your wrist outward until your alms face away from you. At the same time, ully extend arms overhead. Hold for one second. Return to the starting position.</string>
    <string name="shoulder_sdfr">Step 1: Grab a pair of dumbbells take seated position on an incline bench with arms straight and at your sides, thumbs in. / Step 2: Keeping your elbows straight, raise the dumbbells up and forward until your hands are at about eye level / Step 3: Keep the backs of your wrists flat and elbows straight throughout the movement Return to starting position.</string>
    
    Tricep / male
    <string name="tricep_pd">Step 1: Using a high-cable pulley, grasp a short straight bar with an overhand grip. Your hands should be about 10 inches apart. Position your forearms so they are parallel to the floor. Keep your feet shoulder width apart and bend your knees slightly. / Step 2: Keep your elbows locked in close body and your wrists straight. Keep your WHOLE body steady, push the bar as far as possible towards your legs locking your and feeling the triceps full contract. / Step 3: Keep the upper arms close to the body. Return to the starting position using the same motion Never move your elbows or torso! Stay standing straight</string>
    <string name="tricep_e">Step 1: Positioning the bar over your eyes keeps your under some tension while your are in the extended position. / Step 2: Now, keep your upper arms fixed in the extended position while you bend your elbows and allow the weight to descend under control toward forehead.</string>
    <string name="tricep_dte">Step 1: Lie on a flat bench holding a dumbbell in each hand with your arms extended straight up from your shoulders Inhale and slowly bend your arms Return to the starting position, exhaling as you complete the movement. This exercise equally works all the heads of the triceps.</string>
    <string name="tricep_tpd">Step 1: Stand facing the machine with your hands on the bar and your elbows against your sider: Inhale and straighten your arms, but don\'t separate your elbows from your Exhale as you complete the movement.</string>
    <string name="tricep_dp">Step 1: Place yourself position but have your hands placed directly under your chest with your index fingers and thumbs spread and touching so they form a diamond. / Step 2: Keep your back flat as you lower your body until your chest is nearly touching hands. / Step 3: Pause, then push yourself back up to the starting position.</string>
    <string name="tricep_dpob">Step 1: Place yourself in pushup position but have your hands placed directly under your chest with your index fingers and thumbs spread and touching so they form a diamond Keep the toes of your feet on a flat bench. This will put your hands while performing the pushups. / Step 2: Keep your back flat as you lower your body until your chest is nearly touching your hands. / Step 3: Pause, then push yourself back up to the starting position.</string>
    <string name="tricep_cgbp">Step 1: Position yourself on a regular free weight flat bench press machine. Lie flat on your back and grab the barbell above you with a very narrow grip. / Step 2: Focus on keeping about an 6–8 inch width in your grip Lift the barbell off of the rack and lower it to about 3 inches above your chest and then bar back to the start position. / Step 3: Make sure to focus on keeping your elbows in towards your body throughout the full range of the movement.</string>
    
    Leg / male
    <string name="leg_s">Step 1: Place barbell bar across upper back and stand with your feet hip-width apart. / Step 2: Lower your hips until your thighs are parallel to the floor. Push back up all the way, pause, then go back down to parallel. / Step 3: Pause again, then return to the start</string>
    <string name="leg_alp">Step 1: Sit on the machine with your back and head against the padded support. Place feet on the foot plate about hip width apart, ensuring the heels are flat. The legs should form an angle of about 90 degrees at the knee with a little variation either way as long as the heels sit flat on the plate. / Step 2: The knees should be in line with the feet and neither bowed inward nor outward. Your bottom should not be raised from the seat platform. If it is, and the legs are at too sharp angle, then you need to adjust the seat back until the correct position is enabled. You can recognize this floor position when the knees seem to be in front of your eyes and you feel cramped. Grasp the assist handles.</string>
    <string name="leg_dl">Step 1: Stand with dumbbells grasped to sides. Lunge forward with first leg. Land on heel then forefoot. Lower body by flexing knee and hip of front leg until knee of rear leg is almost in contact with floor. / Step 2: Return to original standing position by forcibly extending hip and knee of forward leg. Repeat by alternating lunge with opposite leg.</string>
    <string name="leg_le">Step 1: Slowly raise the weight by extending both legs upwards to the straightened position. / Step 2: Do not jerk the weight up. Hold this position for one second. Slowly lower the weight back to the start position. Repeat movement.</string>
    <string name="leg_ds">Step 1: Stand with your feet slightly apart and grasp dumbbell n each hand with your arms hanging down at your sides Look straight ahead, slightly arch your back, and squat down. / Step 2: Once your things are parallel to the floor, straighten your legs to return to the starting position. Exhale as you complete the movement</string>
    <string name="leg_ps">Step 1: This movement is the same as conventional squats, but your legs are widely spread with your toes pointed outward, which specifically works the inner thighs. / Step 2: The muscles involved are: the quadriceps all the adductors the gluteals the hamstring group all the sacro spinalis muscles.</string>
    <string name="leg_bl">Step 1: Start by placing a barbell across your upper back, use an overhand grip slightly wider than your shoulders. / Step 2: Stand with your feet about 8 inches apart, toes facing forward / Step 3: Take a step forward (2–3 feet) keeping your abs drawn in and your upper body straight. / Step 4: Slowly lower one knee down as if kneeling while keeping your other knee bent at a 90 degrees angle, do not let your knee touch the ground. / Step 5: Lower your body to just above the floor and hold for a moment before returning to the starting position. Repeat with the other leg.</string>
    <string name="leg_slc">Step 1: Sit on the machine with your legs straight, ankles resting on the roller pad. Lower the leg resting over your thighs to secure them / Step 2: Grasp the handles provided on each side: Inhale and bend your knees to move the roller pad downward. Exhale as you complete the movement</string>
    <string name="leg_hs">Step 1: Flex your knees, place your back against the padded surface, wedge your shoulders beat the yokes attached to the machine, and place your feet fairly close together Inhale rotate the stop handles at the sides of the yokes to release the machine, and bend your legs. Step 2: Return to the starting position exhaling as you complete the movement.</string>
    <string name="leg_bj">Step 1: Stand in front of a bench. / Step 2: Jump onto the bench and immediately ump back to the starting position on the floor. / Step 3: Repeat multiple times.</string>
    <string name="leg_sls">Step 1: Stand with your feet shoulder width apart. Lift your stronger or dominant leg straight out in front of your, as high as possible. / Step 2: Such air into the stomach, then push your hips back and squat down as far as possible while keeping your torso as upright as possible. The heel of your front leg can touch the floor at the bottom of the squat, if you can get down that far. / Step 3: Return to the starting position and exhale. Do all your repetitions with your non dominant leg, then repeat with your dominant leg.</string>
    <string name="leg_ic">Step 1: Begin by standing with your feet about shoulder width apart and pointed slightly outwards. / Step 2: Squeeze your glutes and abs, squatting down while raising both of your arms out in front of you until they are parallel to the ground. / Step 3: Continue Squatting until your thighs are parallel to the ground, or as close as you can get to parallel. / Step 4: Maintain this position for the duration of your set.</string>


    Calf / male
    <string name="calf_ts">Step 1: Stand straight with your feet hip-width apart and hold a heavy dumbbell in each hand, arms by your sides. / Step 2: Keeping your back straight, slowly rise up on the toes of both feet, raising your heels as high as you can. / Step 3: Pause at the top, then slowly lower your heels back down.</string>
    <string name="calf_scr">Step 1: Adjust the pad so that your shins are straight up and the pad is just behind the knees. Lift the weight by pushing your heels up with the balls of your feet. / Step 2: Slowly lower the heels until you feel a stretch in the calf muscle. To target inner and outer calves, point your toes inwards and outwards respectively.</string>
    <string name="calf_dcj">Step 1: Stand with your feet hip-width apart. Grab a pair of dumbbells and hold them at your sides at arm\'s length. / Step 2: Dip your knees so they are bent about 45 degrees and jump as high as you can. Point your toes toward the floor when you jump. / Step 3: Allow your knees to bend 45 degrees when your land, then immediately jump again.</string>
    <string name="calf_sbcr">Step 1: While standing with back straight, position barbell on top of your shoulders. Hold barbell with overhand grip. Distance between hands should be wider than shoulder width apart. / Step 2: Raise your calves by tiptoeing. Hold for one second. Lower your calves back to the ground.</string>
    <string name="calf_dbcr">Step 1: Stand straight with your feet hip-width apart and hold a heavy dumbbell in each hand, arms by your sides. / Step 2: Keeping your back straight, slowly rise up on the toes of both feet, raising your heels as high as you can. / Step 3: Pause at the top, then slowly lower your heels back down.</string>

    Bicep / male
    <string name="bicep_bc">Step 1: Starting from the same initial position for standard bicep curl, hold the bar with both arms extended downward, gripping the bar with your palms facing up. / Step 2: Lift the bar, but instead of keeping both elbows locked to your side and lifting in an arc, allow both elbows to move backward in order to "drag" the bar in a straight line directly up the front of your body.</string>
    <string name="bicep_pc">Step 1: Using an underhand grip, hold onto Fa EZ-curl bar. Rest your upper arms on the sloping preacher bench, as illustrated, while holding the bar at an arm\'s length in front. Try to have a slight bend in your elbows. / Step 2: Lift the bar as high as possible while keeping your upper arms firmly planted on the pad. / Step 3: Pause, then slowly return the bar to the starting position.</string>
    <string name="bicep_hc">Step 1: Hold a dumbbell in each hand with your palms and weights facing outward. Your arms should form a 90 degree angle. / Step 2: Keeping your elbow close to your body and in a steady position, curl the weight up towards your shoulder. Lower weights slowly back to starting position.</string>
    <string name="bicep_cc">Step 1: Start by sitting on the edge of the bench holding the dumbbell in your right hand. Let the right arm hang straight down with the elbow resting on the inside of the knee. / Step 2: Lean forward so your torso is over your legs, and place the left hand on the left knee. / Step 3: Bending at the elbow, curl the dumbbell up to shoulder level and pause momentarily before slowly lowering the weight to the starting position.</string>
    <string name="bicep_u">Step 1: Lie prone on the incline bench. Let dumbbells hang next to you with underhand rip. Keep arms straight. / Step 2: Curl the weights slowly straight up. Your wrists should always be fixed, resist twisting them, and keep your upper arms perpendicular to the floor.</string>
    <string name="bicep_sbd">Step 1: While standing with back straight, hold one dumbbell with neutral grip. Rest upper arm on the top of the stability ball. / Step 2: Lift dumbbell up while keeping your upper arms in place. Hold for one second. Lower dumbbell back to starting position.</string>
    <string name="bicep_c">Step 1: Stand with feet about hip-width apart, abs engaged as you hold medium heavy dumbbells in front of the thighs. Squeeze the biceps and bend the arms, curling the weights up towards the shoulders. / Step 2: Keep the elbows stationary and only bring the weight as high as you can without moving the elbows. Slowly lower the weights, keeping a slight bend in the elbows at the bottom (e.g., don\'t lock the joints and try to keep tension on</string>

    Forearm / male
    <string name="forearm_wc">Step 1: Sit with your forearms resting on your thighs or on a bench. Take an underhand grip on the bar with wrists passively extended Inhale and cur your wrist up. / Step 2: Exhale as you complete the movement</string>
    <string name="forearm_dwt">Step 1: Stand with Light Dumbbell in each hand with your arms at your sides, palms facing behind you. Bend your arms to curl the weights up until your forearms are parallel to the floor. This is the starting position. / Step 2: Rotate your wrists until your palms face the ceiling, then back so your the floor once again. Thats one repetition.</string>
    <string name="forearm_swc">Step 1: Grab a barbell behind using underhand grip while keeping your arms straight. Hang the barbell so it rests on your extended fingers. / Step 2: Flex your wrists to raise the barbell up as high as possible. / Step 3: Reverse the movement to lower the barbell.</string>

    Cardio / male
    <string name="jogging">25 minutes for three days a week (you can create your own jogging routine).</string>
    <string name="jumprope">2 minutes for five times a week (you can create your own routine).</string>


    Diets
    <string name="bulk_diet">Aim for a 300- to 400-calorie surplus above your regular calorie
consumption. It might be helpful to track how much you’re eating, on
average, per week before starting a bulk, then add onto that.
• Aim for macros of 25 percent protein, 25 percent fat, and 50 percent
carbohydrates. That said, “it is very important to emphasize that muscle
gains will not occur without being in a calorie surplus even if correct macros
are being met,” Valdes points out.
• Consume at least 1.2 to 2 grams of protein per day per kilogram of
bodyweight. “For example, a 150-pound athlete would weigh 68.2 kilograms
and have protein goals ranging from 80 to 135 grams per day,” Valdes says.
During bulking and aiming for adding lean muscle, you\'d want to shoot for the
high end of the range.
• Space out protein intake throughout the day. “Athletes should space out
protein throughout the day with each meal or snack containing around 20 to
40 grams of protein,” Valdes recommends. Consuming large amounts of
protein at once can often lead to stomach discomfort.
• Eat protein within 30 minutes of strength training. “Protein should be
emphasized within 30 minutes post training and should be paired with a
carbohydrate in a 3:1 ratio of carbohydrates to protein in order to optimize
muscle synthesis and recovery.” She recommends a food like chocolate milk
with 30 grams of carbohydrates and 10 grams of protein.
• Nibble on a quick (but protein-packed) snack before bedtime. “Another
way to meet protein goals could be consuming 25 to 40 grams of protein
before bed to stimulate repair of tissue as opposed to tissue breakdown during
sleep,” Valdes says. “Some evening snack examples could be hard boiled
eggs, cottage cheese, greek yogurt, or a protein shake.” </string>
    <string name="lean_diet">Very low carb diets: A person consumes 20–50 grams (g) of carbohydrates per
day or carbs that make up less than 10% of total daily calories.
• Low carb diets: A person consumes fewer than 130 g of carbohydrates per day or
carbs that make up less than 26% of total daily calories.
• Dash diet: In order to decrease and control high blood pressure and improve general
health, the DASH (Dietary Approaches to Stop Hypertension) diet places an emphasis
on eating fruits, vegetables, whole grains, lean meats, nuts, seeds, and low-fat dairy
products while reducing salt, sweets, and alcohol.
• Plant-based and flexitarian diets: A flexitarian diet combines a predominantly
plant-based approach with the occasional inclusion of animal products in moderation.
Both diets place emphasis on the importance of consuming a variety of fruits,
vegetables, whole grains, legumes, nuts, and seeds to meet nutritional needs.
• The MIND diet: The MIND diet, created to improve brain function and lower the risk of
cognitive decline, stresses a dietary intake concentrated on whole grains, leafy greens,
nuts, berries, fish, chicken, and olive oil, with reduced amounts of red meat and
processed foods.
• The Mediterranean diet: In order to promote overall heart-healthy and balanced
nutrition, the Mediterranean diet places a strong emphasis on a high intake of fruits,
vegetables, whole grains, legumes, nuts, and olive oil, along with moderate
consumption of fish and poultry, and reduced consumption of red meat and sweets</string>

    Butt
    <string name="butt_p">Step 1: First, stand upright with feet positioned wider than shoulder width, toes pointed outward, and arms behind your head. / Step 2: Bend at both your knees and hips, while maintaining a flat back, to enter a squat position with your thighs parallel to the ground. / Step 3: Generate as much power as possible, pushing through your feet until you enter mid-air. / Step 4: Maintain straight legs until the apex of your jump. / Step 5: During the descent, begin to bend at your knees to land in a partial squatting position. / Step 6: Complete subsequent reps starting from step 2.</string>
    <string name="butt_sumo">Step 1: Stand with your feet out wider than your hips, toes pointing out. / Step 2: Raise your arms in front of you at shoulder height, touching. Bend your knees slightly. / Step 3: Holding your arms in this position, squat down until your knees are at a 90 degree angle. / Step 4: In this sumo squat position, lift your right heel up off the floor and bring it back down, then repeat that movement with your left heel. / Step 5: Raise yourself up, straightening your legs, and repeat.</string>
    <string name="butt_cs">Step 1: Stand straight with your feet hip-width apart and your arms to your side. / Step 2: Keep your right foot planted on the ground, while you bring your left foot behind you and off to the side. / Step 3: Bring your arms up, hands aligned with shoulders. / Step 4: Holding this position, lower yourself down to a squat. / Step 5: Pushing through your heel, bring yourself back up and return to starting position. / Step 6: Repeat on opposite sides.</string>

</resources>